[{
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/5ICH-R2dk78AAAAi/wolf-howling.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/5ICH-R2dk78AAAAi/wolf-howling.gif",
    "lvl": 1,
    "question": "Serigala",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/5ICH-R2dk78AAAAi/wolf-howling.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/GDDLB40MtMcAAAAi/squirrel-acorn.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/j4STBrTfPWUAAAAi/chicken-hen.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/VISiRM_3gLoAAAAi/%E8%9E%B3%E8%9E%82-praying-mantis.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/ZwIIFgr4lWoAAAAi/lion-king.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/ZwIIFgr4lWoAAAAi/lion-king.gif",
    "lvl": 2,
    "question": "Singa",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/VISiRM_3gLoAAAAi/%E8%9E%B3%E8%9E%82-praying-mantis.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/NyIz2vSJHBkAAAAi/bat-flying.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/AdXl1uIhQfMAAAAi/turtle-carlbot.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/ZwIIFgr4lWoAAAAi/lion-king.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/7tcTj70SfHAAAAAi/sheep-head-tilt.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/7tcTj70SfHAAAAAi/sheep-head-tilt.gif",
    "lvl": 3,
    "question": "Domba",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/mRHmpBbk4E0AAAAi/pigeon-dove.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/7tcTj70SfHAAAAAi/sheep-head-tilt.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/x7VrAOcZtFoAAAAi/eagle-flap.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/tKPieyYE4NkAAAAi/raccoon-crab-eating-raccoon.gif"
  },{
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/W5qtl0HYoLYAAAAi/catscafe-penguin.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/W5qtl0HYoLYAAAAi/catscafe-penguin.gif",
    "lvl": 4,
    "question": "Pinguin",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/VISiRM_3gLoAAAAi/%E8%9E%B3%E8%9E%82-praying-mantis.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/tKPieyYE4NkAAAAi/raccoon-crab-eating-raccoon.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/W5qtl0HYoLYAAAAi/catscafe-penguin.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/sPcP-WxbX9gAAAAi/bear-american-black-bear.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/kttV6V_t16QAAAAi/horse-joypixels.gif2",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/kttV6V_t16QAAAAi/horse-joypixels.gif2",
    "lvl": 5,
    "question": "Kuda",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/jVwKTebhrcMAAAAi/rak-zwierze.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/lXC19WEAr8IAAAAi/sea-lion-californian-sea-lion.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/BO2F75g_YuIAAAAi/giraffe-stars.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/kttV6V_t16QAAAAi/horse-joypixels.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/7SGlANK3kFEAAAAi/dm4uz3-foekoe.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/7SGlANK3kFEAAAAi/dm4uz3-foekoe.gif",
    "lvl": 6,
    "question": "Ikan",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/9wiJGOH0AjYAAAAi/rats-rat.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/7SGlANK3kFEAAAAi/dm4uz3-foekoe.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/tKPieyYE4NkAAAAi/raccoon-crab-eating-raccoon.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/lXC19WEAr8IAAAAi/sea-lion-californian-sea-lion.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/pQZ0uVs1uv8AAAAi/butterfly-yellow.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/pQZ0uVs1uv8AAAAi/butterfly-yellow.gif",
    "lvl": 7,
    "question": "Kupu-kupu",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/AdXl1uIhQfMAAAAi/turtle-carlbot.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/x7VrAOcZtFoAAAAi/eagle-flap.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/Zyp45ssWB0kAAAAi/rhinoceros-javan-rhinoceros.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/pQZ0uVs1uv8AAAAi/butterfly-yellow.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/keaxDIpKwxcAAAAi/jorrparivar-digital-pratik.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/keaxDIpKwxcAAAAi/jorrparivar-digital-pratik.gif",
    "lvl": 8,
    "question": "Ular",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/keaxDIpKwxcAAAAi/jorrparivar-digital-pratik.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/ffjpRgKzEHYAAAAi/cow-run.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/j4STBrTfPWUAAAAi/chicken-hen.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/BO2F75g_YuIAAAAi/giraffe-stars.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/mRHmpBbk4E0AAAAi/pigeon-dove.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/mRHmpBbk4E0AAAAi/pigeon-dove.gif",
    "lvl": 9,
    "question": "Merpati",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/mRHmpBbk4E0AAAAi/pigeon-dove.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/ZwIIFgr4lWoAAAAi/lion-king.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/pQZ0uVs1uv8AAAAi/butterfly-yellow.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/Zyp45ssWB0kAAAAi/rhinoceros-javan-rhinoceros.gif"
  },{
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/SwqQl1FnAGgAAAAi/owl-blinking.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/SwqQl1FnAGgAAAAi/owl-blinking.gif",
    "lvl": 10,
    "question": "Burung Hantu",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/NyIz2vSJHBkAAAAi/bat-flying.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/mRHmpBbk4E0AAAAi/pigeon-dove.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/yyXO-ZIcUS8AAAAj/animals.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/SwqQl1FnAGgAAAAi/owl-blinking.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/5__8peoJcFoAAAAi/worm-dream-cream.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/5__8peoJcFoAAAAi/worm-dream-cream.gif",
    "lvl": 11,
    "question": "Ulat",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/Zyp45ssWB0kAAAAi/rhinoceros-javan-rhinoceros.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/j4STBrTfPWUAAAAi/chicken-hen.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/mRHmpBbk4E0AAAAi/pigeon-dove.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/5__8peoJcFoAAAAi/worm-dream-cream.gif"
  },
  {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/GDDLB40MtMcAAAAi/squirrel-acorn.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/GDDLB40MtMcAAAAi/squirrel-acorn.gif",
    "lvl": 12,
    "question": "Tupai",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/j4STBrTfPWUAAAAi/chicken-hen.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/sPcP-WxbX9gAAAAi/bear-american-black-bear.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/GDDLB40MtMcAAAAi/squirrel-acorn.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/AdXl1uIhQfMAAAAi/turtle-carlbot.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/AdXl1uIhQfMAAAAi/turtle-carlbot.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/AdXl1uIhQfMAAAAi/turtle-carlbot.gif",
    "lvl": 13,
    "question": "Kura-kura",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/SwqQl1FnAGgAAAAi/owl-blinking.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/AdXl1uIhQfMAAAAi/turtle-carlbot.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/pQZ0uVs1uv8AAAAi/butterfly-yellow.gif ",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/7SGlANK3kFEAAAAi/dm4uz3-foekoe.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/9wiJGOH0AjYAAAAi/rats-rat.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/9wiJGOH0AjYAAAAi/rats-rat.gif",
    "lvl": 14,
    "question": "Tikus",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/9wiJGOH0AjYAAAAi/rats-rat.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/5ICH-R2dk78AAAAi/wolf-howling.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/W5qtl0HYoLYAAAAi/catscafe-penguin.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/kttV6V_t16QAAAAi/horse-joypixels.gif"
  },{
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/x7VrAOcZtFoAAAAi/eagle-flap.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/x7VrAOcZtFoAAAAi/eagle-flap.gif",
    "lvl": 15,
    "question": "Elang",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/W5qtl0HYoLYAAAAi/catscafe-penguin.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/x7VrAOcZtFoAAAAi/eagle-flap.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/Zyp45ssWB0kAAAAi/rhinoceros-javan-rhinoceros.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/AdXl1uIhQfMAAAAi/turtle-carlbot.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/4RBqxp0EVbgAAAAi/camel-dromedary.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/4RBqxp0EVbgAAAAi/camel-dromedary.gif",
    "lvl":16,
    "question": "Unta",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/VISiRM_3gLoAAAAi/%E8%9E%B3%E8%9E%82-praying-mantis.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/1yyaAl88s1UAAAAi/abiera-star.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/4RBqxp0EVbgAAAAi/camel-dromedary.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/GDDLB40MtMcAAAAi/squirrel-acorn.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/NyIz2vSJHBkAAAAi/bat-flying.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/NyIz2vSJHBkAAAAi/bat-flying.gif",
    "lvl": 17,
    "question": "Kelelawar",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/NyIz2vSJHBkAAAAi/bat-flying.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/Zyp45ssWB0kAAAAi/rhinoceros-javan-rhinoceros.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/ffjpRgKzEHYAAAAi/cow-run.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/9uRejMMYygEAAAAi/kangaroo-joypixels.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/BO2F75g_YuIAAAAi/giraffe-stars.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/BO2F75g_YuIAAAAi/giraffe-stars.gif",
    "lvl": 18,
    "question": "Jerapah",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/yyXO-ZIcUS8AAAAj/animals.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/jVwKTebhrcMAAAAi/rak-zwierze.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/lXC19WEAr8IAAAAi/sea-lion-californian-sea-lion.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/BO2F75g_YuIAAAAi/giraffe-stars.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/wScgzw2bMFsAAAAi/tiger.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/wScgzw2bMFsAAAAi/tiger.gif",
    "lvl": 19,
    "question": "Leopard",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/j4STBrTfPWUAAAAi/chicken-hen.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/wScgzw2bMFsAAAAi/tiger.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/tKPieyYE4NkAAAAi/raccoon-crab-eating-raccoon.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/ffjpRgKzEHYAAAAi/cow-run.gif"
  },{
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/Zyp45ssWB0kAAAAi/rhinoceros-javan-rhinoceros.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/Zyp45ssWB0kAAAAi/rhinoceros-javan-rhinoceros.gif",
    "lvl": 20,
    "question": "Badak",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/Zyp45ssWB0kAAAAi/rhinoceros-javan-rhinoceros.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/9uRejMMYygEAAAAi/kangaroo-joypixels.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/sPcP-WxbX9gAAAAi/bear-american-black-bear.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/GDDLB40MtMcAAAAi/squirrel-acorn.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/VISiRM_3gLoAAAAi/%E8%9E%B3%E8%9E%82-praying-mantis.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/VISiRM_3gLoAAAAi/%E8%9E%B3%E8%9E%82-praying-mantis.gif",
    "lvl": 21,
    "question": "Mantis",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/VISiRM_3gLoAAAAi/%E8%9E%B3%E8%9E%82-praying-mantis.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/wScgzw2bMFsAAAAi/tiger.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/keaxDIpKwxcAAAAi/jorrparivar-digital-pratik.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/W5qtl0HYoLYAAAAi/catscafe-penguin.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/tKPieyYE4NkAAAAi/raccoon-crab-eating-raccoon.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/tKPieyYE4NkAAAAi/raccoon-crab-eating-raccoon.gif",
    "lvl": 22,
    "question": "Kukang",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/j4STBrTfPWUAAAAi/chicken-hen.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/tKPieyYE4NkAAAAi/raccoon-crab-eating-raccoon.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/BO2F75g_YuIAAAAi/giraffe-stars.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/x7VrAOcZtFoAAAAi/eagle-flap.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/ffjpRgKzEHYAAAAi/cow-run.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/ffjpRgKzEHYAAAAi/cow-run.gif",
    "lvl": 23,
    "question": "Sapi",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/ffjpRgKzEHYAAAAi/cow-run.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/9uRejMMYygEAAAAi/kangaroo-joypixels.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/SwqQl1FnAGgAAAAi/owl-blinking.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/AdXl1uIhQfMAAAAi/turtle-carlbot.gif"
  },{
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/lXC19WEAr8IAAAAi/sea-lion-californian-sea-lion.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/lXC19WEAr8IAAAAi/sea-lion-californian-sea-lion.gif",
    "lvl": 24,
    "question": "Singa laut",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/jVwKTebhrcMAAAAi/rak-zwierze.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/lXC19WEAr8IAAAAi/sea-lion-californian-sea-lion.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/4RBqxp0EVbgAAAAi/camel-dromedary.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/1yyaAl88s1UAAAAi/abiera-star.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/9uRejMMYygEAAAAi/kangaroo-joypixels.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/9uRejMMYygEAAAAi/kangaroo-joypixels.gif",
    "lvl": 25,
    "question": "Kanguru",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/NyIz2vSJHBkAAAAi/bat-flying.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/4RBqxp0EVbgAAAAi/camel-dromedary.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/9uRejMMYygEAAAAi/kangaroo-joypixels.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/AdXl1uIhQfMAAAAi/turtle-carlbot.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/sPcP-WxbX9gAAAAi/bear-american-black-bear.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/sPcP-WxbX9gAAAAi/bear-american-black-bear.gif",
    "lvl": 26,
    "question": "Beruang",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/sPcP-WxbX9gAAAAi/bear-american-black-bear.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/ZwIIFgr4lWoAAAAi/lion-king.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/5ICH-R2dk78AAAAi/wolf-howling.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/kttV6V_t16QAAAAi/horse-joypixels.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/j4STBrTfPWUAAAAi/chicken-hen.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/j4STBrTfPWUAAAAi/chicken-hen.gif",
    "lvl": 27,
    "question": "Ayam",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/j4STBrTfPWUAAAAi/chicken-hen.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/7tcTj70SfHAAAAAi/sheep-head-tilt.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/pQZ0uVs1uv8AAAAi/butterfly-yellow.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/SwqQl1FnAGgAAAAi/owl-blinking.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/1yyaAl88s1UAAAAi/abiera-star.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/1yyaAl88s1UAAAAi/abiera-star.gif",
    "lvl": 28,
    "question": "Bintang laut",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/JqHpW37XDcsAAAAi/crab-crab-rave.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/jVwKTebhrcMAAAAi/rak-zwierze.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/lXC19WEAr8IAAAAi/sea-lion-californian-sea-lion.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/1yyaAl88s1UAAAAi/abiera-star.gif"
  }, {
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/jVwKTebhrcMAAAAi/rak-zwierze.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/jVwKTebhrcMAAAAi/rak-zwierze.gif",
    "lvl": 29,
    "question": "Lobster",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/7SGlANK3kFEAAAAi/dm4uz3-foekoe.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/JqHpW37XDcsAAAAi/crab-crab-rave.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/jVwKTebhrcMAAAAi/rak-zwierze.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/AdXl1uIhQfMAAAAi/turtle-carlbot.gif"
  },{
    "answer": "https://media.tenor.com/JqHpW37XDcsAAAAi/crab-crab-rave.gif",
    "imgUrl": "https://media.tenor.com/JqHpW37XDcsAAAAi/crab-crab-rave.gif",
    "lvl": 30,
    "question": "Kepiting",
    "CategoryId": 2,
    "optionA": "https://media.tenor.com/5ICH-R2dk78AAAAi/wolf-howling.gif",
    "optionB": "https://media.tenor.com/JqHpW37XDcsAAAAi/crab-crab-rave.gif",
    "optionC": "https://media.tenor.com/ffjpRgKzEHYAAAAi/cow-run.gif",
    "optionD": "https://media.tenor.com/9uRejMMYygEAAAAi/kangaroo-joypixels.gif"
  }
]
  